=Demon Emperor's Matchmaker=
= صانع الثقاب الشيطاني الإمبراطور =
=Episode 21=
= الحلقة 21 =
(The empress called for Chuchu without informing.)
(دعت الإمبراطورة تشوتشو دون إبلاغها).
(Something bad must be happening.)
(يجب أن يحدث شيء سيء.)
Tell me.
أخبرني.
How did you and Li Wuyou work together
كيف عملت أنت و Li Wuyou معًا
to set up His Majesty using witchcraft?
لنصب جلالة الملك بالسحر؟
No.
رقم.
I didn't do anything, Your Majesty.
لم أفعل أي شيء يا جلالة الملك.
You're not going to speak the truth without some torture.
لن تقول الحقيقة بدون بعض التعذيب.
I shall poke you.
سوف أزعجك.
(Chuchu, please be fine.)
(تشوتشو ، من فضلك كن بخير.)
(Wait for me.)
(الانتظار لي.)
Your Majesty, help me.
جلالة الملك ، ساعدني.
Chuchu.
حلمات.
Li Wuyou.
لي وويو.
Listen.
استمع.
Your Majesty wanted to tear my mouth.
جلالة الملك أراد أن يمزق فمي.
She's so scary.
إنها مخيفة جدا.
You don't look like you need help.
لا يبدو أنك بحاجة للمساعدة.
I need it.
أنا في حاجة إليه.
Luckily, you're here in time.
لحسن الحظ ، أنت هنا في الوقت المناسب.
You're rebelling.
أنت تتمرد.
Do you think I'm dead?
هل تعتقد أنني ميت؟
How dare you display your affection here?
كيف تجرؤ على إظهار عاطفتك هنا؟
Where are the guards?
أين الحراس؟
These two are disrespectful.
هذين غير محترمين.
Take them down.
خذهم الى الائسفل.
Yes, Your Majesty.
نعم يا صاحب الجلالة.
Stop.
قف.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Step down.
انزل.
Yes, Your Majesty.
نعم يا صاحب الجلالة.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Empress.
الإمبراطورة.
Look at yourself.
انظر الى نفسك.
It's very inappropriate
إنه غير مناسب للغاية
for an empress to act like this.
للإمبراطورة لتتصرف هكذا.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
I'm just managing the imperial harem for you.
أنا فقط أدير الحريم الإمبراطوري من أجلك.
Why am I wrong?
لماذا أنا مخطئ؟
I govern the empire with benevolence.
أنا أحكم الإمبراطورية بإحسان.
Without forethought,
بدون تفكير
you took someone back for lynching.
لقد أعدت شخصًا لإعدامه دون محاكمة.
Is this how you manage the imperial harem?
هل هذه هي الطريقة التي تدير بها الحريم الإمبراطوري؟
Mother.
الأم.
This time you're wrong indeed.
هذه المرة أنت مخطئ بالفعل.
Wuyou and Chuchu are our family.
Wuyou و Chuchu هم عائلتنا.
Why did you make the situation awkward?
لماذا جعلت الموقف محرجا؟
Wuyou, Chuchu.
Wuyou ، تشوتشو.
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Your Majesty, I'm fine.
جلالة الملك ، أنا بخير.
Pass on my decree.
تمرير مرسوم بلدي.
The empress is grounded for a month,
الامبراطورة على الأرض لمدة شهر ،
so she can reflect on herself
حتى تتمكن من التفكير في نفسها
in the imperial harem.
في الحريم الإمبراطوري.
Li Wuyou. Qiao Chuchu.
لي وويو. كياو تشوتشو.
Curse you!
يلعنكم!
His Majesty is on your side.
جلالة الملك في صفك.
Even my son is on your side.
حتى ابني في صفك.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I... am here... to help... you.
أنا هنا لمساعدتك.
Help... me?
ساعدني؟
I'll... help you... fight... Li... Wuyou.
سأساعدك ... قتال ... لي ... وويو.
These are presents from Mother to you.
هذه هدايا لك من الأم.
Her Majesty?
جلالتها؟
Why is the witch so kind suddenly?
لماذا الساحرة لطيفة جدا فجأة؟
She even give me presents?
حتى أنها أعطتني هدايا؟
No.
رقم.
What I'm saying is,
ما أقوله هو ،
doesn't Her Majesty hate me?
ألا تكرهني جلالة الملكة؟
I don't know either.
لا اعرف ايضا.
Perhaps she has come around it
ربما تكون قد أتت من حوله
and thought she went too far last time.
واعتقدت أنها ذهبت بعيدًا جدًا في المرة الأخيرة.
Hence she's giving you presents as an apology.
ومن ثم فهي تقدم لك الهدايا كاعتذار.
Take them.
خذهم.
Please thank Her Majesty for me.
من فضلك اشكر جلالة الملكة لي.
What are these?
ما هي هذه؟
Why are they so messy?
لماذا هم بهذه الفوضى؟
Li Wuyou, you're back.
لي وويو ، لقد عدت.
What happened? Why are you so happy?
ماذا حدث؟  لماذا أنت سعيد جدا؟
Nothing. I'm happy to see you.
لا شئ.  أنا سعيد برؤيتك.
No wonder you're heavier now.
لا عجب أنك أثقل الآن.
Because the happiness made you fat.
لأن السعادة جعلتك بدينة.
Do you want a piece of me?
هل تريد قطعة مني؟
♪The wind of the early summer♪
رياح أوائل الصيف ♪
♪Created a starry sky♪
♪ خلق السماء المرصعة بالنجوم
♪The dream in my heart♪
الحلم في قلبي ♪
♪Froze at the street intersection in the morning♪
تجمد عند تقاطع الشارع صباحا
♪I've passed the end of the galaxy♪
♪ لقد اجتزت نهاية المجرة
♪I've seen the crowded traffic♪
♪ لقد رأيت ازدحام المرور ♪
♪In my mind♪
♪ في ذهني ♪
♪Your smile is engraved♪
♪ ابتسامتك محفورة ♪